export const questions = [
  // Beginner (preA1) Level
  {
    question: "Are there … pictures … the walls of your bedroom?",
    options: ["any, on, some", "some, on, any", "any, in, some"],
    answer: "any, on, some"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct sentence.",
    options: [
      "He goes usually to the gym on Wednesdays and Fridays.",
      "He usually goes to the gym on Wednesdays and Fridays.",
      "He usually gos to the gym on Wednesdays and Fridays."
    ],
    answer: "He usually goes to the gym on Wednesdays and Fridays."
  },
  {
    question: "… you enjoy doing in your free time?",
    options: ["Where do", "What do", "When are"],
    answer: "What do"
  },
  {
    question: "… you eat breakfast this morning?",
    options: ["Did", "Do", "Were"],
    answer: "Did"
  },

  // A1 / Elementary Level
  {
    question: "I … a nurse, so I … from home.",
    options: ["‘m, ‘m never work", "work, never work", "‘m, never work"],
    answer: "‘m, never work"
  },
  {
    question: "Look! … It’s strange because they don't usually do that.",
    options: [
      "They performing in the street.",
      "They perform in the street.",
      "They are performing in the street."
    ],
    answer: "They are performing in the street."
  },
  {
    question: "How … cups of coffee did you drink this morning?",
    options: ["much", "many", "any"],
    answer: "many"
  },
  {
    question: "Have you ever … an online English course?",
    options: ["taken", "took", "taked"],
    answer: "taken"
  },

  // A2 / Pre-Intermediate Level
  {
    question: "I typically read before bed, …",
    options: ["but tonight I’m watching a movie instead.", "but tonight I watch a movie instead.", "but tonight."],
    answer: "but tonight I’m watching a movie instead."
  },
  {
    question: "I was studying for my exam when the phone…",
    options: ["rang.", "has rung.", "was ringing."],
    answer: "rang."
  },
  {
    question: "In the past, … , but now we can't because we live far apart.",
    options: [
      "I was playing soccer with my friends every evening",
      "I was used to play soccer with my friends every evening",
      "I used to play soccer with my friends every evening"
    ],
    answer: "I used to play soccer with my friends every evening"
  },
  {
    question: "I often come … interesting articles on social media.",
    options: ["across", "with", "over"],
    answer: "across"
  },

  // B1 / Intermediate Level
  {
    question: "Don't worry! The train .. from the station at 9:45 am. We … plenty of time before it leaves.",
    options: [
      "will depart, are having",
      "departs, have",
      "is departing, are having"
    ],
    answer: "departs, have"
  },
  {
    question: "How long … in your current house? - … 3 years already.",
    options: [
      "have you lived, Since",
      "have you been living, For",
      "did you live, For"
    ],
    answer: "have you been living, For"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct reported speech: I saw a shooting star.",
    options: [
      "He said that he had seen a shooting star.",
      "He said that he has seen a shooting star.",
      "He told that he had seen a shooting star."
    ],
    answer: "He said that he had seen a shooting star."
  },
  {
    question: "I wish … It's so irritating!",
    options: [
      "my neighbours would keep their dogs quiet at night.",
      "my neighbours keep their dogs quiet at night.",
      "my neighbours can keep their dogs quiet at night."
    ],
    answer: "my neighbours would keep their dogs quiet at night."
  },

  // B2 / Upper-Intermediate Level
  {
    question: "I … online as it’s become the new normal.",
    options: ["used to study", "’m getting used to study", "’m getting used to studying"],
    answer: "’m getting used to studying"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct sentence.",
    options: [
      "Jack had his bicycle repaired by a mechanic before the race.",
      "Jack was his bicycle repaired by a mechanic before the race.",
      "Jack did his bicycle repaired by a mechanic before the race."
    ],
    answer: "Jack had his bicycle repaired by a mechanic before the race."
  },
  {
    question: "If I … better care of my health in my youth, I … in better shape now.",
    options: [
      "took, would be",
      "took, had been",
      "had taken, would be"
    ],
    answer: "had taken, would be"
  },
  {
    question: "suggest … alternative energy sources for a sustainable future.",
    options: ["use", "to use", "using"],
    answer: "to use"
  }
];